by RentAnAdviser.com
Take a look at my girlfriend
She's the only one I got
Not much of a girlfriend
I never seem to get a lot
It's been some time since
we've last spoke
This is gonna sound like a bad joke
But Momma, I fell in love again
It's safe to say I have
a new girlfriend
And I know it sounds so old
But Cupid got me in a chokehold
And I'm afraid I might give in
Towel's on the mat, my
white flag is wavin'
I mean, she even cooks me pancakes
And Alka-Seltzer when my tummy aches
If that ain't love then I
don't know what love is
We even got a secret handshake
And she loves the music
that my band makes
I know I'm young, but if I had
to choose her or the sun
I'd be one nocturnal son of a gun
Take a look at my girlfriend
She's the only one I got
Not much of a girlfriend
I never seem to get a lot
Take a look at my girlfriend
She's the only one I got
Not much of a girlfriend
I never seem to get a lot
It's been a while since we talked last
And I'm tryin' hard not to talk fast
But Dad, I'm finally thinkin'
I may have found the one
Type of girl that'll make you
way proud of your son
And I know you heard the last song
About the girls that didn't last long
But I promise this is
on a whole new plane
I can tell by the way she says my name
I love the way she calls my phone
She's even got her very own ringtone
If that ain't love then I
don't know what love is
It's gonna be a long drive home
But I know as soon as I arrive home
And I open the door, take off my coat,
and throw my bag on the floor
She'll be back into my arms
once more for sure like
Take a look at my girlfriend
She's the only one I got
Not much of a girlfriend
I never seem to get a lot
Take a look at my girlfriend
She's the only one I got
Not much of a girlfriend
I never seem to get a lot
She's got a smile that'll
make the most senile
Annoying old man bite his
tongue (I'm not done)
She's got eyes comparable to sunrise
And it doesn't stop there
(Man I swear)
She's got porcelain skin,
of course she's a ten
Now she's even got her own
song (But movin on)
She's got the cutest laugh
I've ever heard
And we can be on the phone for three
hours (Not sayin' one word)
And I would still cherish every moment
And when I start to build my future,
she's the main component
Call it (dumb), call it
(luck), call it (love)
Or whatever you call it, but
Everywhere I go I keep her
picture in my wallet like
Take a look at my girlfriend
She's the only one I got
Not much of a girlfriend
I never seem to get a lot
Take a look at my girlfriend
She's the only one I got
Not much of a girlfriend
I never seem to get a lot
by RentAnAdviser.com